Their first meeting was daring. Their last would be deadly.
Zebra Lounge is a thriller film directed by Kari Skogland.
Alan and Wendy Barnet have been married just long enough for the excitement to have gone out of their
relationship, and they're looking for a way to put some spice back in their lives.
After placing a personal ad looking for another couple interested in swapping mates, the Barnets are led to
the Zebra Lounge, where they meet Jack and Louise Bauer, a pair of seasoned erotic adventurers.
While the Barnets find the swinging scene exciting at first, they soon
decide it may be doing more harm than good to their marriage.
But easing the Bauers out of their lives proves to be neither simple nor safe.
Louise Bauer, played by Kristy Swanson.
Jack Bauer, played by Stephen Baldwin.
Wendy Barnet, played by Brandy Ledford.
Alan Barnet, played by Cameron Daddo.
Brooke Barnet, played by Dara Perlmutter.
Daniel Barnet, played by Daniel Magder.
Zebra Lounge is a 2001 erotic thriller directed by Kari Skogland and starring
Kristy Swanson, Stephen Baldwin, Brandy Ledford, and Cameron Daddo.
It was written by Claire Montgomery and Monte Montgomery.
The film explores themes of swinger club,
obsession, marriage, suburbia, romance.
The tone is intense.